我是Abbadon
My name is Abbadon.
是个地狱骑士
Who is a Knight of Hell.
我是你的王
I'm your king.
说到这个
About that.
你又骗了我
You lied to me again.
我也是不得已而为之
I didn't have a choice.
所以呢 你决定骗我同意
So what?You decided to trick me.
被那只精神病天使附身了
And to be possessed by some psycho angel.
我知道你的真实身份
I know who you really are.
Gadreel
Gadreel.
我会作为副手加入你
I will join you as the second in command.
这是你要干掉的第一个人
Here's the first name on your to-do list.
不
No.
如果我救了Sam 你们就还我自由
I save Sam, I leave here a free man.
控制主动权 Sam
Take control, Sam.
把他赶出去
Cast him out.
如果有人因为我而受了伤
The thought of if somebody else get hurt because of me.
这种想法让我一辈子心都不安
I can't live with that.
Kevin的死都怪我
Kevin's blood is on my hands.
我会找到Gadreel
I'll find Gadreel.
亲手杀了那个混蛋
And I will end that son of a bitch.
但我要一个人去
And I'll do it alone.
走吧
Go.
我不会拦着你的
I'm not gonna stop you.
（碧玉泉 密西西比 1863年）
他来了
He's coming.
守好你的岗位 不要轻举妄动
Stand in your ground no matter what happens.
不顾一切保护骑士
The Knight must be protected.
那么
So.
那个色色的笑是献给我的吗
Is that blue smile for me.
先给我买杯喝的如何
Just buy me a drink first.
我说过 等我再看见你
I said that the next time I see you.
我就是死人一个 是啊 我记得
Dead, yes rings a bell.
但我们不要在这儿动手 好吗
But let's not do it in a bar, shall we.
你不会从这儿查到什么的
This bar is a bust.
那边的女服务生倒是跟吸血鬼有一腿
And that waitress is troubled with the capital VD.
至于你的猎物 Gadreel
And your pray, Gadreel.
早就不知道去哪儿了
Has left the building.
是时候考虑下一个重大事宜了
It's time to move on to a more impressing matters.
比如 毁了Abbadon
Like destroying Abbadon.
祝你好运
Good luck with that.
地狱骑士可不是那么容易就杀死的
The Knight of Hell ain't exactly the dying kind.
但是有一件东西能杀死骑士
But there's something can kill a Knight.
大天使们有一件武器
A weapon the archangels used to execute.
初刃
The First Blade.
没听说过
Never heard of it.
我现在能杀你了吗
Can I kill you now.
我找那把匕首已经好久了
I've been chasing that blade for decades.
有一次我差点儿就得手了
The closest I've got to it.
我的人 Smitty
Was when one of my drews Smitty.
听说Abbadon手下的一个恶魔
Got wind of a protage demon of Abbadon's.
知道初刃的消息
Who claimed the acknowledgement of the blade.
遗憾的是 在Smitty下手之前
Sadly, before Smitty could nap the guy.
叫John Winchester的猎人
A hunter by the name of John Winchester.
先他一步做掉了那个恶魔
Nap the protege.
我来找你 是为了看看
I'm here to see.
John Winchester的那本日记
If anything of the John Winchester.
能不能把线索引到初刃上
Memorio bible might lead us to the First Blade.
然后我们就能杀死Abbadon了
To kill Abbadon.
你想跟我一起猎魔
You wanna hunt with me.
我喜欢有个搭档
I do love a good buddy company.
找到了
Yeah here it is.
他干掉了一个
Yeah he picked up the protege.
跟Abaddon不对头的恶魔
Who had bones with Abaddon.
但就这些了
That's all about it is here.
那些数字和符号是什么意思
What are those numbers and marks mean.
不管你的事
None of your business.
你这是在欲擒故纵吗 是蒙太奇手法吗
You playing hard to get?A time for montage.
是密码
It's code.
我父亲的储藏柜之一
One of my dad's story lockers.
为了以防万一 他把东西藏在那里
He made something by the case there.
数字旁边那个T是什么意思
What does that T next to the numbers mean.
不知道
Not a clue.
好吧
Fine.
那我们就去老爸的小窝里翻翻看吧
Let's go find daddy's man cave, shall we.
但我怎么知道这不是个陷阱
But how do I know this isn't a trap.
你不知道
You don't.
这才是有意思的部分
That's what makes it fun.
嘿
Hey.
尝起来像 分子
Tastes like…molecules.
什么
What.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about.
当我是人的时候
When I was human.
为了生存 我必须吃东西
You know, I had to eat constantly.
有点儿小烦人
It was, kind of annoying.
是啊 很多人类的事儿都挺烦人的
Yeah, a lot of human things are pretty annoying.
但是 我享受食物的味道
But…I enjoy the taste of food.
尤其是花生酱
Particularly peanut butter.
还有葡萄果冻 不是果酱
Grape jelly, not jam.
果酱不容易被消化
Jam I found unsettling.
所以呢
So what.
你现在尝不出花生酱果冻了吗
Now you can't taste PB&J.
不是 只是我现在尝到了每个分子的味道
No, I…I taste every molecule.
而不是整体的味道 对吧
Not sum of its parts, huh.
味道太多了
It's overwhelming.
好恶心
It's disgusting.
我真想念你们 花生酱果冻
I miss you, PB&J.
我们需要继续你的治疗
We need to continue your healing.
就快好了
We're almost done.
怎么了
What.
没什么
Nothing.
你不擅长撒谎
You're a terrible liar.
错
That's not true.
我曾经
I once deceived.
把你们兄弟俩骗的团团转
And betrayed both you and your brother.
好了 这不是重点
Okay it's not the point.
Cass 到底出什么事儿了
Cass, what's wrong.
我发现
I notice something it's.
你身体里有东西产生了共鸣
It's resonated inside you.
什么
What.
与天使有关
Something angelic.
好吧
Okay.
什么意思
What the hell does that mean.
我们应该给Dean打电话
Maybe we should call Dean.
不
No.
他想走就叫他走好了
He wanted to go and he's gone.
这事儿不要叫上他
We'll handle this.
真的有必要吗
Is all this really necessary.
我好歹也在你弟身体里待过
I mean I've been inside your brother.
我们可是沾亲带故呢
We're practically family.
听着
Listen to me.
你与我跟亲人这个词差了十万八千里
We are the furthest thing from family.
明白了吗老混蛋
You got that dickbag.
明白
Oh yeah.
你不是来猎魔的吗 我们现在就开始吧
Now you wanna hunt, let's hunt.
我就在这儿待着
I'll be right here.
话说回来 你们这种装修风格叫什么
What do you call this decor anyway.
乡巴佬强迫症
Rustic obsessive.
多疑症患者室内布置
Paranoid deco.
找到了
Here we go.
目测我爸抓住
Looks like my dad was.
Abbadon的小罗喽的时候
Working with another hunter.
正跟另一个猎人在一起
When he nabbed Abbadon's pet.
所以那个T不是指世界第一废柴老爹喽
I guess the T didn't stand for terrible father.
它代表了
It stood for.
Tara
Tara.
没什么想法
Doesn't ring a bell.
好吧
All right.
看起来他们审讯了一个恶魔
Looks like they interrogated a demon.
然后驱逐了它
And then they exorcise him.
但是恶魔交待了有关初刃的消息
But not before he mentioned the First Blade.
我就知道我是对的
I love it when I'm right.
剩下的文件都是空白的 天才
The rest of the file was empty, genius.
猎人霍格沃茨难道不教你们如何记好笔记吗
Didn't they teach note taking in the hunters Hogwarts.
我们去找Tara看她是不是还活着吧
Let's go see if Tara's still kicking.
找到了
I found something.
上面描述了
It's a detail about when.
天使离开容器之后的细节
Angels leave their vessels.
大概是这样 这是天使语
I think, it's…Enochian.
写得文绉绉的
Which can be a bit flowery.
弃之亦留
And the departed shall remain.
留之为弃
And the remains shall be the departed.
好吧
Okay.
所以天使离开容器的时候
So when angels leave their vessels.
会有一部分留下
They leave behind a piece of themselves.
比如就像 天使的指纹之类的
Like a…like an angelic fingerprint.
随便你想怎么说
Whatever you wanna call it.
被留下的那一部分
This piece of the departed.
有残余的荣光
Contains grace.
你是说 我身体里还有天使残存的荣光
Are you saying that there's an angelic grace inside of me.
是的
Yes.
我帮你治疗一次 它的力量就减弱一分
But it's fading each time I heal you.
这是好事儿还是坏事儿
Okay, is that good or bad.
它是无害的
Well, it's harmless.
但这一部分荣光或许能帮到我们
The grace itself might be helpful.
根据这份资料
According to this.
我们或许可以用你身体里的荣光
We maybe able to use the grace that.
追踪到Gadreel
Remains inside you to track Gadreel.
如果能提取出来
If we can extract it.
要怎么做
How would we do.
这么说吧
Well.
很痛苦
Painfully.
学者们相信有了荣光
The Men of Letters believed that you could perform a.
就能制造一个追踪咒语
Tracking spell with the extracted grace.
但他们从来没有证实过可行性
They were never able to test the theory.
那是因为他们没有小白鼠 不过我们正好有
Well, they didn't have a guinea pig, we do.
你什么时候养了只小白鼠
You have a guinea pig.
在哪儿
Where.
我是说我 Cass
Me, Cass.
我就是小白鼠
I'm the guinea pig.
知道那东西在哪儿吗
Any idea with where that is.
你是Tara吗
Tara.
牌子上就是这么写的
It's what the sign says.
两位需要帮助吗
Can I help you.
我希望你能有所帮助
Yeah, I hope so.
John Winchester 有印象吗
John Winchester, ring a bell.
我是他儿子
I'm the son.
你是Sam还是Dean
Are you Sam or Dean.
Dean
Dean.
你倒是长成个俊俏模样
Well, didn't you grow up pretty.
还在干你们的家庭事业吗
Still in the family business.
是啊 从小就被教育出来了
Yeah, born and raised.
说正事 几年以前
Listen, bunch of years back.
你和我爸一起猎过魔
You worked a job with my dad.
我和我的 呃 同伴
Well, me and my, uh, associate.
自从92年开始 只要我周围有恶魔
Ever since 92 I get a painful little tickle.
我的膝盖就会一阵痒
In what's left in my knee whatever a demon is around.
这就是猎人 多么相互信任
Hunters, so trusting.
你们俩谈吧 我去买杯拿铁
I'll go grab a latte while you get this sorted.
那条仿波斯毯底下画着恶魔陷阱呢 混蛋
Devil's trap under the knock-off Persian, jackass.
Tara
Tara.
听着 我的 同伴
Listen, my…uh associate.
其实是好哥们儿
Besties, actually.
帮倒忙
Not helping.
我不在乎
Not caring.
听着 我是地狱之王
Look, I'm the King of Hell.
他是个Winchester
He's a Winchester.
我们俩之所以在一起肯定事出有因
There's a reason why we're working together.
是啊
Yeah.
我管那叫恶魔附身
It's called possession.
瞧见没 我没被附身
See?I'm good.
好了吗
Okay.
你说的没错
Yes, you're right.
他确实是个混蛋
He's a jackass.
但是他在帮我忙
But he's helping me on this.
帮你做什么
Helping you with what.
你和我老爹曾经捉住过一只恶魔
You and my old man found a demon.
它知道初刃的消息
Who knew something about the First Blade.
我们需要那把匕首
We need to find that blade.
见鬼
Well, hell.
你跟John一样有着漂亮的脸蛋
You are as handsome as John.
要是你也想找那把匕首 那你就和他一样蠢了
And as dumb too if you're looking for that old relic.
我们在追杀一个地狱骑士
We're hunting a Knight of Hell.
为什么 他们不都死光了吗
Why?They're all dead.
其中一个复活了
One came back.
Abaddon
Abaddon.
那个恶魔说大天使们有一件武器
The demon said the archangels used a weapon.
可以杀死地狱骑士
That could kill the Knights of Hell.
但我们从没听说过什么地狱骑士
We'd never heard of anything like the Knights of Hell.
更别说是初刃了
Or a First Blade.
你老爹觉得他在说谎
Your dad thought he was lying.
只为了逃过杀身之祸
Trying to save himself.
所以我们就驱逐了他
We took him out.
我和你老爹度过了愉快的一周末
And we had a lovely weekend together.
然后我们就分道扬镳了
Then we went our separate ways.
但我对那个匕首念念不忘
But I could never let the blade go.
要知道那种东西
Something like that.
能对猎人帮上很大忙
Could really give a hunter an edge you know.
我四处寻找线索
I looked all over the world.
以我的膝盖和我这辈子作为代价
Destroyed my knee and my life.
最后我找到了什么呢
And all I found.
初刃的坐标咒语
A location spell for the blade.
但我永远都无法完成这个咒语
That I could never finish.
其中一样材料凑不齐
Couldn't find one ingredient.
挪威海怪的精髓
Essence of Kraken.
挪威海怪
Kraken.
我在伯利兹有一仓库的挪威海怪收藏
I got a warehouse full of Kraken essence in Belize.
破坏掉这个陷阱
Break the trap.
我能在你们说presto之前就能跑个来回
I can be there and back before you say presto.
Presto
Presto.
我能帮你们 Dean你来
I can help, Dean.
他和我一样想要Abaddon死
He wants Abaddon as dead as I do.
如果你老爹知道你在干什么
If your daddy could see you now.
即使那个什么初刃真的存在
You know, even if that blade is real.
那也不值得你跟
It ain't worth being.
地狱之王勾肩搭背
Bosom buddies with the King of Hell.
只要能杀死Abaddon 没有什么不可以
Abaddon?Way worse.
等这事儿过了我再解决Crowley
I'll deal with Crowley after.
相信我
Trust me.
你跟你老爹听起来一模一样
You sound just like your dad.
当他说要打给我的时候
When he said he'd call me.
能开始了吗
Shall we.
密苏里州 找到了
Missouri, figures.
要加入我们吗
Would you care to join us.
他 随时可以
Him?Anytime.
你 想都别想
You?Never.
谢谢
Thank you.
祝你好运 Dean
Good luck, Dean.
你会需要这个的
You're gonna need it.
等等
Wait.
怎么了
What.
我感觉到了什么
I'm dealing something.
你害怕了
Oh, cramps.
我感受到了一股黑暗的力量
I feel something dark.
什么 比你还黑
What, darker than you.
哦 完蛋了
Oh, no.
我们必须马上离开
We need to leave here now.
什么 你对密封过敏还是怎么的
What, are you allergic to bees.
那不是个养蜂人
That's not a beekeeper.
那是谋杀之父
That's the father of murder.
抱歉 谁
Sorry, who.
Cain
It's Cain.
你是说Cain和Abel那个Cain
As in Cain and Abel.
Dean
Dean.
我们必须马上离开这儿 离开他
We need to be a world away from here, from him.
你们哪儿也去不了
You're not going anywhere.
Crowley
Crowley.
你怎么不直接飞出去
Why don't you just zap out out of here.
我从来不会放下我的伙伴不管的
I never leave my domestic partner in crime.
说的就好像你突然性情大变了似的
Yeah, like your heart grew three sizes.
你出不去 对吧
You can't zap out of here, can you.
Cain对我有影响
Cain's doing something to me.
看来今天不适合你跑路啊 是不是
It's not your day for getaway, isn't it.
告诉我Cain的事
All right, so tell me about this Cain.
Cain把Abel杀了之后 就变成了恶魔
Well, the Cain killed Abel and became a demon.
你说 变成了恶魔 是什么意思
What do you mean became a demon.
就是他变成了不死的恶魔
I mean he became the deadliest demon.
在地球上游荡
To walk the face of the earth.
残杀万千
Kill thousands.
最好的堕落成最邪恶的
The best being the worst.
然后他就
Then he just.
消失了
Disappeared.
所有人都以为他死了
Everyone thought he was dead.
大家都这么想
At least hoped he was.
你们俩有谁养过蜂吗
Do either of you keep bees.
有益于身心放松
It's very relaxing.
蜜蜂 多么高尚的生物
They're such noble creatures.
他们产的蜂蜜
And the honey.
我都留在了蜂房上
Well, I keep it right on the comb.
给
Here you are.
他们快死了
They're dying, you know.
没有了蜜蜂 人类到头来只有一死
Without bees, mankind will cease to exist.
话说回来
So.
地狱之王
What are the king of hell.
和Winchester来我家干什么
And Winchester doing at my house.
你知道我们是谁
You know who we are.
我虽然退休了 但是还没死
I'm retired.I'm not dead.
我不知道的是
What I don't know.
为什么你们在找我
Is why are you looking for me.
最重要的是
More importantly.
你们是如何找到我的
How you found me.
其实 呃 有个小故事
Ah, it's a…funny story really.
还有一点点的误会
Bit of misunderstanding.
我们真的
We really.
你一定要教我这招儿
You are gonna teach me how to do that.
你来这儿的目的是什么 Dean
Why are you here, Dean.
我们在找一件武器
We're looking for the weapon.
大天使用来杀地狱骑士的武器
The archangel uses to kill the knights of hell.
初刃
The first blade.
我们需要干掉一个地狱骑士
We needed it to kill a knight of hell.
Abaddon
Abaddon.
好吧 我懂 你退休了
Okay, I get it.You're retired.
我们不是来破坏
We're not here to get between.
你恶魔式的退休生活的
You and the demonic AARP.
但外面情况很乱
But it's bad out there.
我只是在找赢的机会
I'm just looking the even of odds.
最后问你一次
One last time.
你是怎么找到我的
How did you find me.
不是我们找到了你
We didn't.
是初刃的坐标咒语把我们引到了这里
The location spell was for the blade.
咒语只能生效一次
One time deal.
还有人知道你们在这儿吗
Anyone else knew you're here.
没有
No.
打扰一下
Excuse me, ma'am.
请问你有没有
Wonder if you might have seen.
看到我的朋友经过
Some of my friends pass through here.
一个男的
The guy.
长着奇怪的耳朵
Kind of funny ears.
很高兴有人拜访
Well, it's been a pleasure having company.
但是一百年里有一次也就够了
But once a century is enough for me.
出门不送
You can let yourselves out.
听着
Hey listen pal.
没拿到初刃我们不会走
We're not leaving here without the blade.
Dean 你的名声我听说过
You have a quite reputation, Dean.
我也看到了你的勇气
I see the part of you being brave rings true.
我能说什么
Well, what can I say.
我就是对一件事件紧咬不放
I'm an all-in kinda guy.
Abaddon是最后一个地狱骑士
Abaddon is the last knight of hell.
如果你早就什么都不管了
And if you're out of game.
那她死了 你也无所谓吧
What the hell do you care if she dies.
如果你的朋友能说话 他会告诉你
If your friend can talk, he could tell you.
地狱骑士是我亲自训练的
That I trained the knights of hell.
我自己亲手建立起的
I built that demonic order.
恶魔军队 包括Abaddon
With my own hands, Abaddon included.
呃 这种消息
Well, that is information.
5分钟之前你就该说了
I could've used five minutes ago.
还有一些事你朋友不知道
Here's something your friend doesn't know.
其实除了Abaddon以外没人知道
That no one knows in fact, outside Abaddon.
地狱骑士其实不是大天使杀死的
It wasn't the archangel that slaughtered the knights.
是我干的
It was me.
你为什么突然杀同族
Why did you turn on your own.
我很欣赏你的勇气
Once again, I admired your bravery.
不好意思
But if you excuse me.
我要去城里办点事
I have errands to run into town.
再见Dean Winchester
Goodbye, Dean Winchester.
永远不要回来
Never return.
还真是愉快啊
Well, that was lovely.
现在我们能出国逃命了吗
Can we leave the country now.
你说 初刃是我们唯一
You said the first blade was our.
杀死Abaddon的机会
Only shot to kill Abaddon, this is.
现在又是离成功最近的一次
The closest you've been to it.
我们不走
We’re not leaving.
你就不能听听话 一次也行啊
Will you listen to reason, for once.
他说他要进城
Hey, he said he was going into town.
正好
Awesome.
等他一走
We wait till he's gone.
我们就闯进去 拿走东西
Come back, bust it, take what's ours.
明白了吗
Got it.
Sam 我能问你一个问题吗
Sam, may I ask you a question.
你刚问了
You just did.
那我能再问你一个问题吗
Can I ask you another question.
呃 严格来说 好啊
Well, technically…yeah.
问吧 怎么了
Go ahead, what's up.
Sam 试炼的时候
Sam, the trials.
你选择
You chose.
不完成试炼 对不对
Not to go through with them for a reason, didn't you.
你选择 活下去
You chose to live.
而不是牺牲自己
Rather than to sacrifice yourself.
你和Dean
You and Dean.
- 你们选择对方 - 是的
- You chose each other - Yeah, I did.
我们以前是
We did.
然后 Dean替我做了一次选择
And then, Dean made a choice for me.
- Dean所做的 - 他做了什么已经不重要了
- What Dean did - Doesn't matter what Dean did.
我本来可以阻止一切
Look, I could have stopped all this Cass.
本来可以关上地狱之门
I could have closed the gates of hell.
Sam
Oh Sam.
Dean自己走的
Dean's gone, okay.
现在这一切都算在我的头上
This is on me now.
如果我找到Gadreel
If I can find Gadreel.
就还有扭转的机会
I can fix this.
现在
Now.
做为一个人类
Being a human.
就意味着要及时还债
Means settling your debts.
我们一起平衡收支吧
Let's start balance the books.
这可真是
This is by far.
目前为止 你做过最蠢的决定了
The dumbest thing you've ever had.
这么说还太早
Yeah, well, it's early.
什么都没有
Oh…it's nothing here.
真遗憾 走吧
Shame.Let's go.
嘿 好好的开始找行不行
Hey, sack up and start looking okay.
没多少时间了
We don't have much time.
你绝对不会相信Winchester和Crowley发现了什么
You'd never believe what Winchester and Crowley found.
求支援
Send back up.
把所有人都派过来
Send everyday.
很快就要开始疼了
Now come to the part where it actually hurt.
我要开始提取了
I'm gonna begin the extraction.
这么做有用吗
Is it working.
是的
Yeah.
但是
But.
我还要扎深一点
I need to push the needle in deeper.
施这个咒语
We need more grace in order to.
我们需要更多的荣光
Cast this about.
那就继续吧
Okay do it.
- Sam 如果我不小心 - 靠 Cass
- Sam, if I get too close - Damn it, Cass.
别废话 快做
Just do it.
怎么回事
What the hell was that.
你的身体正在恢复
Your body is regressing to the state.
Gadreel附身之前的状态
It was in before Gadreel.
有足够的荣光了吗
Do we have enough grace for summoning spell.
Sam
Sam.
到底有没有 Cass
Do we or not, Cass.
没有
No.
那就继续
Then keep going.
什么都没有
Nothing.
连A片都没有
Not even porn.
我知道他为什么
I can figure out why.
隐姓埋名了这么多年
He went out reservation so many years ago.
小美人
Lovely.
不过有点儿苍白 她是谁
Little Plain?Who is she.
Cain手上有相同的戒指
Cain had a similar ring on.
谋杀之父成家了
Father of murder got hitched.
他回来了 快走
He's back, come on.
那是我的
That belongs to me.
抱歉
Sorry.
她很漂亮
Gorgeous, by the way.
是你的人吧
I suppose that was with you.
不是
No.
我们等不及了
Guess we can't wait any longer.
你的朋友Tara帮了我们很多
Your friend Tara was very helpful.
聊了很多
Got downright chatty.
在我剥了她的皮之后
After I peeled all her skin off.
我们不想惹麻烦Cain
We don't want any trouble, Cain.
只要你交出那个所谓的地狱之王和Winchester
Just want so called King and the Winchester.
我要讨好我的新主人
I got a new master to impress.
我猜那两个家伙正好够用了
And I'm betting bagging those two will do.
就那样
Just that.
主人
Master.
Abaddon
Abaddon.
这些人死定了
This lot all need to die.
我数数
I count.
太多了
Too many.
你在门上做的手脚能把我们关在里面
The whammy you put out the door keeps us in.
能把他们挡在外面吗
Can it keep them out.
暂时可以
For now.
我去找东西把门堵上
I'm gonna barricade the entrances.
准备好战斗
You're ready for a fight.
你们加油
Well, good luck with that.
什么
What.
你暴露了我家
You exposed my home.
暴露了我
You exposed me.
呵呵
Well, boohoo.
有勇气但是很讨厌
Brave but repulsive.
你还真是如别人所说
You truly have adopted your reputation.
但你就有点儿名不副实了
I can't say you've lived up to yours.
我能说什么
What can I say.
我退休了
I'm retired.
你要是能活下来
You survive.
欢迎你和我一起
You're welcome to join me.
共享最后一餐
For last meal I leave this house.
然后我就会彻底消失
Before I disappeared again.
我也只能做到这些了
It's the least I can do.
Sam Sam
Sam Sam.
继续
Keep going.
为什么
Why.
我们必须找到Gadreel
We have to find Gadreel.
不
No.
为什么Winchester总是把自己往死路上逼
Why must the Winchesters run towards death.
别
Don't…don't.
别停
Don't stop.
Sam 在我 还是人的时候
Sam, when I…was human.
我死过 那份经历让我知道生命的可贵
I died, that showed me life is precious.
生命是必须用尽全力去保护的
And it must be protected by all causes.
就算
Even if life is.
就算你的生活和Winchester一样糟
Is pigheaded as Winchesters.
我的生活比你们任何人
My life's not worse any more than.
都要糟
Anyone else's.
不管是你 还是Dean 还是Kevin
Not yours, or Dean's, or Kevin's.
求你
Please.
帮我做一件对的事吧
Please help me do one thing right.
继续
Keep going.
这边有我
All right, I got this.
你去前面
You take the front.
这就是你的计划
So, this is your play.
玉米
Corn.
我怎么就弄不明白
What am I not getting here.
你也不像是个懦夫
I mean, it's not like you're a coward.
从什么时候开始 伟大的Dean Winchester
Since when does the great Dean Winchester.
开始求人了
Ask for help.
听起来可不像是我在
That doesn't sound like the man.
厕所墙上的故事里读到的那个人
I've read about on demon bathroom walls.
也许你落了一步
Maybe you've lost a step.
我们来看看
Let's find out.
别管我
Don't mind me.
你们玩儿好
Enjoy yourself.
目前还不错
Doing great.
来真的吗
Really.
这会儿不应该过了你的上床时间了吗
Isn't it past your bedtime.
你是很厉害
You're good.
但老子是Crowley
But I'm Crowley.
这是什么 你在考验我吗
What was it?Some kind of a test.
我从一开始就觉得
I felt connected to you.
我们之间有联系
Right from the beginning.
同样的灵魂
Kindred spirits, if you will.
你和我很像
You and I are very much alike.
嗯
Right.
但是我没杀我弟弟
Yeah, except I didn't kill my brother.
你救了你弟弟
You saved yours.
为什么
Why.
因为我们从来不会放弃家人
Because you never gave up on family.
永运都不会
Ever.
那你弟弟现在在哪儿
Where's your brother now, then.
我不知道你耍的
I don't know what kind of game.
什么把戏 我也不在乎
You're playing here, I don't really care.
快给我初刃
Just give me the damn blade.
不好意思 Dean
Sorry, Dean.
我没什么能给的出手
I have nothing to hand over.
什么意思
What.
我没有初刃
I no longer have the blade.
早就不在我这儿了
It's gone.
等等
Hold on.
可能有点疼
This may pinch.
Cass
Cass.
怎么回事
What the hell.
Cass
Cass.
怎么了
What the hell was that.
我治好了你所有的伤
I've healed your wounds completely.
荣光呢
And the grace.
在你体内的荣光已经没有了
Well, whatever grace was inside you is gone now.
Gadreel留下的全在这里了
What's left of Gadreel is in here.
现在我们只能用现有的资源试上一试了
We'll just have to try the spell with what we have.
该死的
Damn it.
Sam 我和你一样想惩治Gadreel
Sam, I want Gadreel to pay as much as you do.
但是没有任何事值得牺牲你自己
But nothing is worth losing you.
作为人类的经历
Being human, didn't just.
不仅改变了我对食物的态度
Change my view of food.
也改变了我对你的看法
It changed my view of you.
我现在能理解 你的感受了
I mean I can relate now, of how you feel.
你的意思是
What are you talking about.
唯一一个犯错
The only person who has screwed things up.
比你还频繁的人
More consistently than you.
就是我了
Is me.
现在 我知道负罪感是什么了
And now, I know what that guilt feels like.
我现在知道内疚是一种什么感觉了 Sam
And I know what it means to feel sorry, Sam.
我很抱歉
I am sorry.
我知道
I know.
要是以前的我
You know, the old me.
我只会一直向前
I would've have just kept going.
会把针一直刺到你脑子深处 直到你死
Would have jammed that needle in deeper until you died.
因为我为了目的总是不择手段
Because the ends always justify the means.
但是 我所经历的
But, what I went through.
花生酱果冻教会我
That PB&J taught me that.
天使也能改变
Angels can change, so.
谁知道呢
Who knows.
也许Winchester兄弟也可以
Maybe Winchesters can, too.
不在了
Gone.
你什么意思 不见了
What do you mean, gone.
怎么会
How.
咒语把我们带到了这里 找到了你
The spell brought us here, to you.
肯定不会错的
So it has to be here.
你的咒语把你带到了初刃的力量之源
Your spell brought you to the source of the blade's power.
我
Me.
不是吧 现在祈祷
Really, now.
这是该死的Cain的印记
It's the bloody mark of Cain.
是Lucifer亲手印下的
From Lucifer himself.
印记和初刃同时使用才能起效
The mark and the blade work together.
没有印记 初任刃毫无作用
Without the mark, the blade is useless.
只是根老骨头而已
It's just an old bone.
骨头
Bone.
动物的颌骨
The jaw bone, of an animal.
你用来杀死Able的颌骨
A jaw bone you used to kill Abel.
因为他是上帝最宠爱的孩子
Because he was God's favorite.
Abel当时不是在和上帝交流
Abel wasn't talking to God.
他是在和Lucifer交流
He was talking to Lucifer.
Lucifer会让我弟弟变成他的走狗
Lucifer was gonna make my brother into his pet.
我无法亲眼看着他堕落
I couldn't bear to watch him be corrupted.
所以我提出了一个交易
So I offered a deal.
我的灵魂下地狱 Abel的灵魂留在天堂
Abel soul in heaven for my soul in hell.
Lucifer接受了
Lucifer accepted.
前提是我亲手送Abel的灵魂上天堂
As long as I was the one who sent Abel to heaven.
所以我杀了他
So I killed him.
成为了地狱的战士
Became a soldier of hell.
地狱的骑士
A knight.
接着Lucifer让你继续送地狱的灵魂上去
And Lucifer ordered you to make more.
我和我的骑士们
My knights and I.
我们做了很多令人发指的事
We did horrible things.
几个世纪都是如此
For centuries.
我们带来陷入混乱和黑暗
Bringers of chaos and darkness.
然后你遇到了Colette
Then you met Colette.
她知道我是谁
She knew who I was.
知道我是什么
What I was.
但还是无条件的爱我
She loved me unconditionally.
她原谅了我
She forgave me.
她只有一个要求
She wanted to ask for one thing.
停止这一切
To stop.
骑士们发现之后 开始报复
When the knights found out, they took retribution.
他们带走了Colette
They took Colette.
所以我重新拿起初刃
So I picked the first blade back up.
把它再次握在手中的感觉妙不可言
It felt so good to have it in my hands again.
然后我杀了地狱骑士们
And I slaughtered the knights of hell.
没杀干净
Not all of them.
没有
No.
Colette
Colette.
亲爱的
My love.
你把我妻子怎么了
What have you done to my wife.
回答我 Abaddon
Answer me, Abaddon.
我们可以挽回错误
We can make this right.
对吗 Cain
Can't we, Cain.
回到我们之中
Come back to us.
回到我身边
Come back to me.
我早不干了
I'm done.
不当骑士 还是离开我
With the knights, or with me.
我不干了
I'm done.
她也不用活了
And so is she.
不 住手
No, stop it.
我们本可以永远相伴的
We could have been forever.
但是你选择了她
But you chose her.
如果我不能拥有你
Well if I can't have you.
那她也不能
Then neither can she.
喜欢这个画面吗
Enjoying the view.
我很喜欢
I know I am.
我可是看得一清二楚
Best seat in the house.
不 Colette
No, Colette.
Colette 我很抱歉 对不起
Colette, I'm sorry.I'm so sorry.
我会找到Abaddon 然后杀了她
I will find Abaddon and I'll kill her.
不 已经有太多的杀戮
No, there has been enough killing.
答应我 你的生命比这些有价值得多
Promise me, you're better than all of this.
我安葬了她之后就离开了
So I buried her and I walked away.
我很抱歉 真的
Well, I am sorry, truly.
但是我得阻止Abaddon
But I have to stop Abaddon.
初刃在哪里
So, where is the blade.
不
No.
听着 混蛋
Hey, listen, you son of a bitch.
你不想开杀戒 但我没这么说过
You may be done with killing, but I am not.
你永远都不懂得放弃 是不是
You never give up on anything, do you.
绝不
Never.
但是我懂
Well, I do.
Cain
Cain.
我会尽量拖住他们的
I'll stay as long as I can.
你真是逗人爱
Aren't you a peach.
我尽力了
I've tried.
我尽全力 Colette 用你的方式看待我自己
I've tried, Colette, to see myself as you did.
但是我知道我是谁
But I know who I am.
知道我的本性
What I am.
我知道你一直在守护我
I know you watch over me, still.
但是我需要你无视我一下
But I need you to look away now.
搞什么啊 伙计
What the hell, man.
你到底干不干
You're in or out.
我头都晕了
I'm getting head-spins.
我可以把印记给你 Dean
I can give you the mark, Dean.
如果你真的想要的话
If it's what you truly want it.
你这话什么意思
What are you talking about.
印记可以传给值得拥有它的人
The mark can be transferred to someone who's worthy.
给和你一样的杀手
You mean a killer like you.
对
Yes.
- 我可以用它杀死那个贱人吗 - 是的
- Can I use it to kill that bitch - Yes.
但是你得清楚 印记
But you have to know with the mark.
会给你带来负担
Comes a great burden.
会给你带来不小的伤害
Someone called it a great cost.
好的 省省这些友情提示吧
Yeah, spare me the warning.
能杀死那贱人就够了
You had me at kill the bitch.
Dean 祝好运
Good luck, Dean.
你需要好运
You're gonna need it.
这话我听多了
I get that a lot.
好戏开始
Let's dance.
Dean
Dean.
我没事
I'm fine.
好吧
All right.
你把那个该死的初刃藏哪里了
Where the hell did you stash the damn blade.
没有东西能摧毁初刃
Nothing can destroy the blade.
所以我把它藏在了大洋的最深处
So I threw it into the bottom of the deepest ocean.
只有这样我才能信守我对Colette的承诺
It's the only way I can keep my promise to Colette.
找到初刃 杀了Abaddon
You find the blade.Kill Abaddon.
但是首先要答应我
But make me a promise first.
我召唤你的时候 我一定会召唤你
When I call you, and I will call.
你来找我 然后把刀用在我身上
You come find me, and use the blade on me.
为什么
Why.
因为我接下来要做的事
For what I'm about to do.
他们都困在里面了
They're all trapped in there.
他也是
With him.
这样就好了吗
Was that it.
荣光的量太少了
I'm afraid there wasn't enough grace.
我们得用其它办法找Gadreel了 对不起 Sam
We'll have to find Gadreel another way.I'm sorry, Sam.
没事
It's all right.Cass.
你说的对
You're…you're right.
你说的都对
You were right about everything.
你应该也抱住我才对
Now's the part where you hug back.
哦 抱歉
Right, sorry.
这就对了
There you go.
就我所知
As far as I'm concerned.
Metatron是纠正一切的关键
Metatron is the key to fixing everything.
不应该这样 我会找到他
That's wrong.I'm gonna find him.
Sam
You know, Sam.
我们需要动用一切帮助
We could use all the help we could get.
来找到Gadreel和Metatron
To find Gadreel and Metatron.
我们能行的
We got this.
他说的对
He was right, you know.
你值得拥有那个标记
You are worthy.
好极了 你也开始煽情了
Great, now you're gonna get all touchy feely too.
你的问题 在于你是世界上最恨你自己的人
Your problem, is that nobody hates you more than you do.
相信我 我试过了
Believe me, I've tried.
我们怎么找这个初刃
So how do we find this blade.
你不能搜遍所有的海底 但是我可以
You can't search the bottom of the ocean, but I can.
我会找到它 然后把它送到它新主人的手上
So I'll find it, and bring it to its new owner.
我都看到了 Crowley
I saw you, Crowley.
在Cain家的时候
Back at Cain's.
你除了那个攻击你的恶魔
You dusted that undercard demon.
然后就坐在那儿
And then you just sat back.
旁观了这一切
And watched the main event.
你早就知道
You knew.
你知道印记的事
You knew about the mark.
知道Abaddon和Cain的事
You knew Abaddon and Cain.
你知道所有的事
You knew all of it.
你耍了我
And you played me.
为什么
Why.
他永远不会把初刃给我的
He would never have given me the blade.
但是谁会对你说不呢
Who can say no to you.
我得让你演下去
I needed you to play along.
你知道我们被跟踪了
You knew we were being followed.
但你什么都没说
But you didn't say anything.
Cain想让我们看他
Well, Cain would want we were to see.
重归战场
His prize fighter up close.
你加恶魔 等于 不战不归夜
You plus demons equals fight night.
Tara死了
Tara died.
因为你而死
Thanks to you.
蛋卷 打鸡蛋 等等等等
Omelets.Broken eggs.etc.
我杀了Ababddon之后
After I killed Abaddon.
你就是下一个
You're next.
你这话不是真心的
You don't mean that.
我们一起多欢乐啊
We're having too much fun.
听着 就算有了初刃
Listen up, even with the blade.
我们也得用尽所有能用的手段
We're gonna need all the help we can get.
来对付Abaddon
To against Abaddon.
去找初刃吧
Go find the blade.
你们两兄弟之间总要有点儿事 对吧
It's always something with you boys, isn't it.